Episode 6
World-Splitter Gladius
This is the first person from the
other dimension we've encountered.
Her identifier is Aldea.
The name of her Magitech armor is Zeeru.
It appears similar to a Heart Hybrid Gear,
but its special ability
allows it to warp space.
So this is what reflected the Pulverizer?
And this is what trapped us before, right?
She said the Batlantis Empire
lies beyond the Entrances.
Is that the enemy that's sending
in the Magitech weapons?
We don't know yet.
We've named the three-headed dragon Tri-Head.
Since its power vastly exceeds
that of a Category-A weapon,
we've designated a new Super-Category Class.
Commander!
We should head back there right away!
No.
This mission is complete.
Why?!
That Magitech weapon is dangerous!
We can't just let it sit out there!
We infiltrated enemy-occupied territory
for the first time,
found a new type of Magitech weapon,
and discovered, plus made contact with,
otherworld people.
That's more than enough for one mission.
I can't accept that!
We should wipe them out
with everything we have!
What's gotten into you, Himekawa?
Nothing!
I'm just suggesting the obvious!
And if we capture that person
from the other dimension,
we can get more information!
Calm down, Hayuru.
If we go without a plan,
we'll just lose again.
Getting cold feet, are we?
After all that bragging about being
the American ace and the strongest?
What did you say?
Hida-kun, you understand, right?
Well...
I'm disappointed in you!
Okay.
Himekawa?
It can't be.
Oh my.
You came back by yourself?
Where is that Magitech weapon?
You're not interested in me at all?
How rude.
Well, not like you're the one
I'm after, either.
Zeeru.
I've got questions for you, too!
I'll play with you.
Come on.
Blades!
That strange technique again...
I'll show you something even more fun.
Labyrinth Cube!
Wh-What's this?
The Labyrinth Cube, an inescapable prison
made by warping space.
I control everything that happens inside.
I know, I can slice the space inside into
tiny little pieces and rearrange them.
It will rip your body apart.
You'd better let our little kitty cat go
or you're going to have a big problem!
Himekawa!
You idiot! That was crazy!
H-Hida-kun... But why?
I can't let you fight alone!
We're on the same team!
You need to die, too.
You really are amazing.
Hey, would you tell me your name?
You should be grateful that I'm telling you.
Aine Chidorigafuchi.
A-Aine?
Would you tell me the name
of that Magitech armor, too?
Magitech armor?
What's that?
This is a Heart Hybrid Gear.
Zeros.
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
Were these your last words?
It didn't make any sense to me!
H-Hey!
Jeez...
You guys can play with him.
There it is.
If your Magitech armor really is Zeros,
then show me your power.
How dare you?!
Hey!
Don't push yourself too hard.
Your Hybrid Count!
You idiot!
What kind of fool leaves without permission?!
Sis!
Kurumizawa.
Roger.
Kizuna, Climax Hybrid!
The love room!
Let's go, Himekawa.
Himekawa...
I'm a terrible person!
I try to correct everyone else's behavior,
but I cause more trouble than everyone else.
My selfishness put my team in danger!
In the end, I'm no better than this.
Himekawa, what happened with you
and that Magitech weapon?
It's not my first time...
...fighting that Magitech weapon.
During the second world collision,
my mission was to escort
the evacuees aboard the Megafloat.
That's when that Magitech weapon appeared.
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything!
If I had more power...
If I was stronger...
I could've protected them!
I was just being arrogant because
everyone said I was Japan's ace.
I did so many interviews,
went to so many parties,
that I didn't train as much as I should have.
If I'd trained harder
and gotten stronger,
I could've saved many lives!
I don't want to make that mistake ever again!
I control myself, discipline myself,
live an ordered life,
abandon my worldly desires,
and train every day
so that I can give everything
I have to my mission.
That was how I decided I'd live.
But...
But you shouldn't just focus on
the lives you couldn't save.
There were lots of lives you did save.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Where can I find someone like that?
Right in front of you.
When I first came to Ataraxia,
you saved me from the attack
by that Viking, right?
B-But even if I hadn't saved you—
I couldn't fight back then.
You saved me,
which is why I was able to
save Yurishia and Aine later.
You've saved a lot of people.
You just don't realize it.
That's not...
I know how you feel.
What could you possibly know?
I had a Heart Hybrid Gear,
but I couldn't fight.
I had to protect other people,
but in reality,
I couldn't even protect myself.
But now,
if the two of us work together, we can fight.
If we Climax Hybrid and bring out the
Immoral Weapon lying dormant within you,
we can defeat Tri-Head.
We can defeat Tri-Head?
Yeah.
If we work... together?
Will you do it?
No...
Your breasts are very shapely.
Can you show them to me?
I don't know how you can say something
so lewd with a straight face.
You think my breasts are small, don't you?
That's not true.
You're lying.
I know you compare them
to Aine-san's and Yurishia-san's!
N-No! Not there!
N-No, I can't!
You're sensitive, aren't you?
N-No, th-this is...
Your breasts are every bit as good
as Aine's and Yurishia's.
R-Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
N-No!
N-No! This is too embarrassing!
So this is a Heart Hybrid...
It's like the whole world's changed.
We're just getting started.
Hida-kun, what is this?
I prepared a situation I thought you'd like.
Th-This is...
I don't like this!
No!
Himekawa, are you okay?
Yes, but...
Don't touch me there too much!
I-I told you no!
Himekawa, this isn't...
I-I don't meow!
Don't ask!
It's nothing! It's nothing!
Don't pull it!
Okay.
Are you okay, Himekawa?
I'm fine.
So don't touch my tail anymore.
I'm sorry, Himekawa.
We have to make our
Climax Hybrid a success.
So this is a Climax Hybrid...
What is that?
Neros!
Gladius!
Hayuru Himekawa! Here I come!
I'll never forget how I
failed to protect Japan,
or all the people I couldn't save,
or that girl's smile.
But I won't let it stop me anymore!
Begone.
In one hit?
What the hell is that?
I could tell you,
but there are things we
want to know from you!
I just saw how you move,
so I think it'll be difficult!
Eros has no weapons.
Is there no point in doing
a Climax Hybrid with it?
If I had Neros's weapon...
Is this...?
What?
Neros's blade?
It's probably an effect of his
Climax Hybrid with Himekawa.
But...
...does this mean Eros is also
capable of creating matter?
That's an interesting power you've got.
Blades!
There's nowhere left to run.
I didn't expect this to be so much fun.
I'm glad I came to Lemuria after all.
Enemy battleship incoming!
500-meter class!
Three more of them!
And four 1000-meter classes!
So many—
2000-meter class, incoming!
Now we get serious.
It's time to kill.
Is that...?
What's that?
Is that from the other dimension?
Nope.
They're allies.
That light...
America's Heart Hybrid Gear unit.
The Masters.
This is getting even more fun.
Now, let's dance—
Aldea.
You're satisfied, right?
Come back.
Grabel.
What are you doing here?
I came to capture an idiot
who disobeyed orders...
...and broke regulations.
Don't be a wet blanket.
Things are just about to get good.
Aldea!
Fine.
The enemy fleet is retreating
into the Entrance!
It's a message from Megafloat West USA.
"Hi, girls. The cavalry is here.
Now that we're here, you're safe.
Start choosing your dresses
for the victory party."
Ask them what they're doing here.
Um, what are you doing here?
Huh?
You're tracing a mysterious radio signal?
So the same thing as us?
Did that fleet come just to get Aldea?
I'm curious about the other dimension.
But I'm more curious about Hayuru.
Wh-What?
You clearly did a Climax Hybrid, didn't you?
No way.
Hayuru never shuts up about
how she hates lewd things.
No, it's impossible.
I can't believe anybody but me could
do a Climax Hybrid with Kizuna.
I did!
Kizuna and I, together!
But I didn't have a choice
because it was for my mission!
I won't let you do anything
indecent that's not necessary.
What?
Now there's nothing for us to do.
Well, I guess they must have
gotten scared of us and ran.
Scarlet?
It's been forever.
You seem to be doing well.
Stay away!
I'm never going to forgive you.
Illustration: Shonan Ruizu
Hi, everybody!
It's Scarlet, from the Masters!
Now that we're here, everything will be okay!
No matter what enemy may come,
I'll send them to hell with a single shot!
Next time: Imperial Hero -Grabel-
Yurishia, I won't let you
beat me no matter what!